Ana-Louise Trinidad

Email: ana3nity.ux@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://ana3nity.github.io/ux-portfolio/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ana-louise-trinidad/

| Bay Area, CA |

I have accumulated 1 year of valuable experience in UX for Social Impact, BioTech, and Gaming. I aspire to blend my passion in technology to create impactful solutions for marginalized, vulnerable communities while enhancing user experience.

Technical Skills

UX/UI Design Tools: User Research, User Interviews, Problem Spotting, Critical Thinking, Site Maps, Affinity Diagrams, Storytelling, Empathy Development, Usability Testing, Visual Design

Technical: Figma, Notion, Trello, HTML, CSS, GitHub, Bootstrap, Visual Studio Code, Atom

Work Experience

Web Design, User Experience Intern Castix LLC - Project Medieval Lands Starting September 2023

- Collaborate closely with the development and design teams to create a website that effectively promotes the upcoming game launch.
- Prioritize user experience by considering navigation, interaction flows, and accessibility.
- Perform a competitive analysis of other game-related websites to identify industry trends, best practices, and innovative design approaches.

Front-End Designer Intern SereneX LLC - Cognitive Behavior Research for Healthcare

August 2023 - Present

- Collaborate with the design team to create visually appealing and user-friendly designs for web and mobile applications. Assist in the development of wireframes, prototypes, and mockups.
- Support the design team in implementing design changes and improvements based on feedback and user testing.
- Contribute to the creation and maintenance of design assets, style guides, and other design-related documentation.

- Stay up-to-date with design trends, industry best practices, and emerging technologies.

Filipino Advocates for Justice Outreach Worker, UX Designer, Wordpress Front-End Developer

March 2022 - Present

- UX/UI Capstone Project turned into freelance opportunity; Website revamp
- Skills | Technologies Used: User Experience Design (UI/UX), Site Maps, Information Architecture, User Interviews, Usability Testing, Survey Creation, Stakeholder Interviews, Teamwork Collaboration

Highlighted Project

San Jose Strong App | User Researcher & UX Designer

- User Researcher:
 - Creation of Internal Database User Survey, Usability Testing Plan, Script, and Ouestions
- Web Dev Committee roles:
 - Assigned a portion of the website building-process using Webflow
 - Developing parts of the website from referencing High-Fidelity prototypes from the web designer
- App Dev Committee roles:
 - Contribute in making improvements to the app by usability testing

Volunteer

Literacy Alliance Wordpress Front-End Developer

August 2023 - Present

• Implementing the completed High-Fldelity Wireframes by the volunteer UX Designers to Literacy Alliance's website on Wordpress while collaborating with the Back-End Developer

Education

Building Mobile Apps with HTML5 Certificate *Ed2Go* | *Mission College Santa Clara*

August 2023 - Present

Certificate in UX/UI Design
University of California, Berkeley Extension

April 2023

Bachelor of Arts in General Biology San Francisco State University

May 2018